<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Joey Jooste</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Joey Jooste</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OODA Loop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/oodaloop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/oodaloop/</guid>
      <description>The OODA loop is a decision-making framework developed by military strategist John Boyd. It stands for Observe, Orient, Decide, and Act.
Observe The first step, gather information from your environment. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s physical or related to a problem you are having. You have to start by gathering all the information you can.
Orient Analyse it. Mentally process all the information and position yourself in the context of the information. How does it affect you?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency = Winning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/consistency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 22:56:51 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/consistency/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m chronically ADHD. Staying consistent has always been one of the hardest things for me to do. I find it nearly impossible to build habits that last. The second I miss a single day of any habit I fall apart.
The solution to building habits, that last for me, has been one thing. Only trying to build 1 habit at a time. The constant mistake I was making was trying to change too many things at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Market Research</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-importance-of-market-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 22:16:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-importance-of-market-research/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Market Research
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t sound very interesting, yet it&amp;rsquo;s increasingly important. I made the mistake today of not researching a market well enough before entering it. Specifically not researching the market in my country.
What happened I made the decision at my company to target boxing gyms with our product offering. The issue with this, is that in the UK boxing gyms are more like clubs, that have sponsors and receive donations, unlike the US where boxing gyms are businesses which you can sell too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Day or Day One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/one-day-or-day-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 16:39:16 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/one-day-or-day-one/</guid>
      <description>Introduction One day or day one&amp;hellip;
One of my favourite motivational quotes.
It&amp;rsquo;s extremely cliche, but it&amp;rsquo;s true, it applies to nearly all things you want to start.
Today I did my first 6 proper cold calls.
I had been putting if off for a long time and today was the day I finally decided to do it properly.
You are going to be awful You are going to suck, its your first day, no one is a master at it on their first day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My first month on Arch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/my-first-month-on-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:30:28 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/my-first-month-on-arch/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Arch for about a month now. It has been the best experience that I&amp;rsquo;ve had while using a computer.
And its not even close.
The beginnings Growing up I played a lot of video games, so naturally I gravitated towards windows. I also didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of money. This combination meant I was using windows and always attempting to squeeze the most performance possible out of it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
